 #require_relative "card"

 #require 'active_record'
 

 # data = Class.new


cards =  []
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 6 * 8", answer: "48")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 8 * 8", answer: "64")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 32 * 35", answer: "1120")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 6 * 8", answer: "48")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 93 * 4", answer: "372")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 9 * 5", answer: "45")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 420 * 420", answer: "176400")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 47 * 10", answer: "470")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 99 * 98", answer: "9702")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 12 * 365", answer: "4380")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 365 * 24", answer: "8760")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 60 * 24", answer: "1440")
cards << Card.create(question: "what is 100 * 100", answer: "10000")





